Energizing brands and enlivening nights, I embody the fusion of digital mastery and musical flair. My expertise in creating compelling online narratives is matched by my passion for music as a DJ who fuels the crowd's fire. With my finger on the pulse of social trends and my hand on the DJ deck, I'm ready to elevate the company presence to an unforgettable experience.



# PONGSIN PONGWACHIRINT UI/UX DESIGNER DIGITAL MARKETING DJ/PRODUCER

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2022 - Present

Illumination Company Limited | 55/41 Plex Residence Kaset-Nawamin, Bangkok Thailand

#### **CONSULTANT**

provides advice and guidance on a variety of business matters, including developing and implementing strategic plans, improving operational efficiency, increasing sales and profitability, expanding into new markets, launching new products or services, managing change and transition, resolving complex problems, and making better business decisions.

2020 - 2022

Colver Glove Company Limited | 1999/9 Sriwara District Bangkok Thailand

#### MANAGING DIRECTOR

Managing for a clover glove company is to manage the company's operations and resources to achieve its goals and objectives, grow its business, and become a leader in the medical glove industry. We have accomplish to have 510(k) certificate for FDA United State.

2016 - 2020

Live Application Company | Bigo Live, Kitty Live, Tutu Live

#### PROJECT MANAGING DIRECTOR

Responsible for the online and offline events for the platform of live application. Manage VJ agency to push the VJs to do their job on the company policy. Bigo Live have success in thai market for live application, kitty live also have success from the campaign that have execute.

#### CONTACT



+66 64 924 4991



PONGSIN.P@JAROENDEEKHUEN.COM



772/156 NOBEL REMIX THONGLOR 36 BANGKOK THAILAND

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

MICROSOFT OFFICE

PREMIERE PRO

**ILLUSTRATOR** 

**PHOTOSHOP** 

**GENERATIVE AI** 

#### **PRO SKILLS**

- SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGEMENT
- PROJECT MANAGEMENT
- GRAPHIC DESIGN
- DJ/PRODUCER

#### **EDUCATION**

1992-2004

**GENERAL DEPLOMA DEGREE** 

Ekamai International School

2004-2005

**COMPUTER SCIENCE** 

Assumption University

# WORK EXPERIENCE (CONTINUED)

2018 - 2020

Naver Corporation Korea (Snow App) | Oversea Contract

#### MARKETING EXECUTIVE (OVERSEA)

Responsible for hiring, arranging, and managing international and local famous stars and artists to create viral content for the Snow App platform. This is an important role because it helps Snow App to reach a wider audience and promote its platform in a creative and engaging way.

2016 - 2018

Winner Online Co., Ltd. |

#### ONLINE GAME CONTENT MARKETING

Responsible for the gaming content to reach out the players and stable the community of the online game. Responsible for offline and online competition for the online game that we have provide.

2014 - 2016

Me Management Co., Ltd. | Hi5 Angel

#### **EVENT MANAGER & GRAPHIC DESIGNER**

Responsible for the event that will happen in the platform and make a magazine that sell in the market of Thailand. Responsible for planning and executing a concert tour for an artist, while a graphic designer might be responsible for designing the tour's branding and promotional materials. Another example is an album release event, where an event manager might be responsible for planning and executing the event, while a graphic designer might be responsible for designing the album cover and other promotional materials.

#### REFERENCES

#### **Kittimes Tanadechruangroj**

CEO | Illumination Company Limited

- **4** +66 61 656 5994
- popjager@iws.co.th

#### Watson Homsangpradit

CEO | Me Management Co., Ltd.

- **466 91 724 9499**
- boywatson.handmade@gmail.com

# Kongphob Kantathavorn

CEO | Clover Glove Company Limited

- **4** +66 63 836 6999
- kkpob02@gmail.com

#### **Siravit Chen Xing**

Coo | Tutu Live

- +66 90 951 5940
- ChenXing@gmail.com

# SOCIAL

F

FACEBOOK: DJ.BAZIO



LINKEDIN: BAZIOVIP



MIXCLOUD: DJBazio2

# LANGUAGE

ENGLISH

(Native Language)

THAI

(Native Language)

# **AWARDS & CERTIFICATE**

2023

Foundations of UX/UI Design

Coursera

2023

**Google Ads Certifications** 

Google

2022

**Clover Glove pre-market 510(k)** 

FDA US

# **INTERESTS**



Newspaper Reading



Online Gaming



Landscape Photography



Internet Browsing